City of Newburgh Urban Renewal; Collection apap375
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Appraisals, 1935-1987; 2; 21 cubic ft.
  - 3-2-4, 43 Montgomery St., Lot 14, 1972-1976 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Block 3-2-4, Parcel 14, 43 Montgomery Street (NYR 189), 1973 (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - 3-2-4, 45 Montgomery St., Lot 13 (NYR 189), 1968-1971 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - 3-2-4, 47 Montgomery St., Lot 12 (NYR 189), 1951; 1970-1972 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - 3-2-4, 49 Montgomery St., Lot 11 (NYR 189), 1951; 1958; 1970-1971 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - 3-2-4, 51 Montgomery St., Lot 10 (NYR 189), 1948; 1968; 1970-1971 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - 3-2-4, 53 Montgomery St., Lot 9 (NYR 189), 1970-1971 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - 3-2-4, 55 Montgomery St., Lot 8 (NYR 189), 1958; 1964; 1970-1971 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - 3-2-4, 57 Montgomery St., Lot 7 (NYR 189), 1958; 1966; 1970-1973 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - 3-2-5, 71-75 Montgomery St., Lot 54-56 (NYR 189), 1957; 1966; 1971 (Box 3, Folder 38)
  - 3-2-4, 76-78 Montgomery St., Lot 15 (NYR 189), 1963-1964; 1970-1973 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - 3-2-5, 77-89 Montgomery St., Lot 50-53 (NYR 189), 1964-1967; Undated (Box 3, Folder 37)
  - 3-2-5, 91 Montgomery St., Lot 49 (NYR 189), 1962; 1966 (Box 3, Folder 36)
  - 3-2-5, 101-107 Montgomery St., Lot 45-48 (NYR 189), 1968-1969; 1972-1974 (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - 3-2-5, 109 Montgomery St., Lot 44 (NYR 189), 1966; 1970-1973 (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - 3-2-5, 111 + 111A Montgomery St., 42+43 (NYR 189), 1952; 1966 (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - 3-2-5, 117 Montgomery St., Lot 39-40 (NYR 189), 1951; 1966 (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - 3-2-5, 119 Montgomery St., Lot 36-38 (NYR 189), 1966 (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - 3-2-5, 121 Montgomery St., Lot 35 (NYR 189), 1946; 1966 (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - 3-2-5, 123 Montgomery Street, Lot 34 (NYR 189), 1952; 1966 (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - 3-2-5, 125 Montgomery Street, Lot 33 (NYR 189), 1947; 1966; 1970-1971 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - 3-2-5, 127 Montgomery, Nathan Pollock (NYR 189), 1953; 1971-1972; Undated (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - 3-2-5, 129 Montgomery St., Lot 31 (NYR 189), 1953; 1966 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - 131 Montgomery Street, DMB 3-2-5, Lot 30, 1975 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - 4-1-1, 140 Montgomery St., Lot 24 (NYR 189), 1970-1972 (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - 4-1-1, 142 Montgomery St., Lot 23 (NYR 189), 1947; 1966-1970 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - 4-1-1, 144 Montgomery St., Lot 22 (NYR 189), 1970-1972 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - 4-1-1, 146 Montgomery St., Lot 21 (NYR 189), 1960-1970 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - 4-1-1, 148 Montgomery St., Lot 20 (NYR 189), 1960; 1969-1971 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - 4-1-1, 150 Montgomery St., Lot 19 (NYR 189), 1959; 1970 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - 4-1-1, 152 Montgomery St., Lot 18 (NYR 189), 1970-1971 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - 4-1-1, 154-156 Montgomery St., Lot 16-17 (NYR 189), 1958; 1966; 1970-1972 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Block 4-1-3, Parcel 1, 158-160 Montgomery Street (NYR 189) (1 of 2), 1974 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Block 4-1-3, Parcel 1, 158-160 Montgomery Street (NYR 189) (2 of 2), 1974 (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - 4-1-3, 162 Montgomery St., Lot 2 (NYR 189), 1966-1973 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Block 4-1-3, Parcel 2, 162 Montgomery Street (NYR 189) (1 of 2), 1974 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Block 4-1-3, Parcel 2, 162 Montgomery Street (NYR 189) (2 of 2), 1974 (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - 4-1-3, 164-166 Montgomery St., Lot 3-4 (NYR 189), 1952; 1966; 1972-1974 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - 4-5-2, 167-173 Montgomery St. 38-43, Lot 171/2 (NYR 189), 1970-1973; Undated (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - 4-1-3, 168-170 Montgomery St., Lot 5-6 (NYR 189), 1952; 1966; 1970-1972 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Block 4-1-3, Parcels 5 and 6, 168-170 Montgomery Street (NYR 189) (1 of 3), 1974 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Block 4-1-3, Parcels 5 and 6, 168-170 Montgomery Street (NYR 189) (2 of 3), 1974 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Block 4-1-3, Parcels 5 and 6, 168-170 Montgomery Street (NYR 189) (3 of 3), 1974 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - 168-170 Montgomery Street, Julius and Ann Johnson Property, 1974 (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - 168-170 Montgomery Street, 5 and 6, Julius and Ann Johnson Property, 1974 (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - 4-1-3, 172-174 Montgomery St., Lot 7-8 (NYR 189), 1966; 1968-1971 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Block 4-1-3, Parcels 7 and 8, 172-174 Montgomery Street (NYR 189), 1974 (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - 4-1-3, 176-178 Montgomery St., Lot 9 (NYR 189), 1966; 1970-1971 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Block 4-1-3, Parcel 9, 176-178 Montgomery Street, 1971 (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Block 4-1-3, Parcel 9, 176-178 Montgomery St. (NYR 189), 1974 (Box 8, Folder 29)
  - 176-178 Montgomery Street, Solomon and Mamie Ware Property, 1974 (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - 4-1-3, 186-188 Montgomery St., Lot 9 (NYR 189) (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - 4-1-3, 180 Montgomery St., Lot 10 (NYR 189), 1965-1966 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - 4-1-3, 182 Montgomery St., Lot 11 (NYR 189), 1962; 1966 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - 4-1-3, 184-192 Montgomery St., Lot 12-14 (NYR 189), 1960; 1966 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - 4-6-2, 193-195 Montgomery St., Lot 63 (NYR 189), 1966 (Box 2, Folder 55)
  - 4-2-1, 194-200 Montgomery St., Lot 1-3 (NYR 189), 1953; 1966; 1971 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - 4-2-1, 202 Montgomery St., Lot 4 (NYR 189), 1953 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - 4-6-2, 203-205 Montgomery St., Lot 58-59 (NYR 189), 1966 (Box 2, Folder 54)
  - 4-2-1, 204 Montgomery St., Lot 5 (NYR 189), 1969-1972 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - 4-2-1, 206 Montgomery St., Lot 6 (NYR 189), 1954-1966 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - 4-6-2, 207-2k3 Montgomery St., Lot 55-57 (NYR 189), 1966 (Box 2, Folder 53)
  - 4-2-1, 208 Montgomery St., Lot 7 (NYR 189), 1966 (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - 4-2-1, 210-214 Montgomery St., Lot 8-10 (NYR 189), 1961; 1969-1972; 1976-1977 (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - 4-6-2, 215-17 Montgomery St., Lot 53-54 (NYR 189), 1966 (Box 2, Folder 52)
  - 4-2-1, 216-218 Montgomery St., Lot 11-12 (NYR 189), 1962; 1966 (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - 4-6-2, 219-225 Montgomery St., Lot 49-52 (NYR 189), 1966 (Box 2, Folder 51)
  - 4-2-1, 222 Montgomery St., Lot 13 (NYR 189), 1955; 1970-1973 (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - 4-6-2, 227-35 Montgomery St., Lot 45-48 (NYR 189), 1966 (Box 2, Folder 50)
  - 4-2-1, 228-234 Montgomery St., Lot 15 (NYR 189), 1970-1974; Undated (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - 235 Montgomery Street, Sylcox Nursing Home (NYR 189) (1 of 2), 1970 (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - 235 Montgomery Street, Sylcox Nursing Home (NYR 189) (2 of 2), 1970 (Box 8, Folder 28)
  - 235 Montgomery Street, Real Estate Appraisal, Sylcox Nursing Home, 1970 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - 235 Montgomery, Real Estate Appraisal, Sylcox Nursing Home (NYR 189), 1970 (Box 8, Folder 27)
  - 235 Montgomery, Appraisal Report, Sylcox Nursing Home (NYR 189), 1970-1971 (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - 4-2-1, 236 Montgomery St., Lot 16 (NYR 189), 1958; 1966 (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - 237 Montgomery Street, Appraisal Sylcox Nursing Home (1 of 2), 1974 (Box 19, Folder 18)
  - 237 Montgomery Street, Appraisal Sylcox Nursing Home (2 of 2), 1974 (Box 20, Folder 21)
  - 237 Montgomery Street, Sylcox Nursing Home, Newburgh, 1974 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - DMB 4-6-2 Lot 41-44, 237-241 Montgomery Street, Edward Sylcox, 1974 (Box 19, Folder 16)
  - 4-6-2, 237-247 Montgomery St., Lot 41-44 (NYR 189), 1966-1975 (Box 2, Folder 49)
  - 4-2-1, 238 Montgomery St., Lot 17 (NYR 189), 1966 (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - 4-2-1, 240 Montgomery St., Lot 18 (NYR 189), 1943; 1971-1973 (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - 4-2-1, 242-244 Montgomery St., Lot 19-20 (NYR 189), 1969-1970 (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - 248 Montgomery St., Lot 21 (NYR 189), 1964; 1971-1973 (Box 4, Folder 35)
  - 4-6-2, 249-253 Montgomery St., Lot 38-40 (NYR 189), 1966 (Box 2, Folder 48)
  - 4-2-1, 252 Montgomery St., Lot 22 (NYR 189), 1955; 1966 (Box 4, Folder 36)
  - 4-2-1, 254 Montgomery St., Lot 23 (NYR 189), 1955; 1966 (Box 4, Folder 37)
  - 4-6-2, 255 Montgomery St., Lot 37 (NYR 189), 1966 (Box 2, Folder 47)
  - 4-2-1, 256 Montgomery St., Lot 24 (NYR 189), 1966 (Box 4, Folder 38)
  - 4-6-2, 257-59 Montgomery St., Lot 35-36 (NYR 189), 1966 (Box 2, Folder 46)
  - 4-2-1, 258 Montgomery St., Lot 25 (NYR 189), 1966; 1969-1972 (Box 4, Folder 39)
  - 4-3-1, 260-264 Montgomery St., Lot 1-3 (NYR 189), 1969-1971 (Box 4, Folder 43)
  - 4-3-1, 266-270 Montgomery St., Lot 4-5 (NYR 189), 1969-1971 (Box 4, Folder 44)
  - 4-3-1, 272 Montgomery St., Lot 6 (NYR 189), 1966-1970; Undated (Box 4, Folder 45)
  - 4-3-1, 274 Montgomery St., Lot 7 (NYR 189), 1966; 1969-1970 (Box 4, Folder 46)
  - 4-3-1, 276-280 Montgomery St., Lot 8-10 (NYR 189), 1969-1970 (Box 4, Folder 47)
  - 4-3-1, 282 Montgomery St., Lot 11 (NYR 189), 1970-1972 (Box 4, Folder 48)
  - 4-3-1, 284 Montgomery St., Lot 12 (NYR 189), 1970-1971 (Box 4, Folder 49)
  - 4-3-1, 288 Montgomery St., Lot 14 (NYR 189), 1966-1970 (Box 4, Folder 51)
  - 4-3-3, 308 Montgomery St., Lot 10 (NYR 189), 1970 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - 4-3-3, 310-312 Montgomery St., Lot 11 (NYR 189), 1968-1971 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - 4-3-3, 314 Montgomery St., Lot 13 (NYR 189), 1960; 1970 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - 4-3-3, 29-33 Nicoll St., Lot 16-22 (NYR 189), 1970 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - 4-3-3, 35 Nicoll St., Lot 14-15 (NYR 189), 1959-1970; Undated (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - 2-5-5, Second St., Lot 8A (NYR 189), 1972-1975 (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - 2-5-5, 67 Second St., Lot 32 (NYR 189), 1972-1976 (Box 9, Folder 27)
  - 2-5-5, 71 Second St., Lot 34 (NYR 189), 1945; 1966; 1971 (Box 9, Folder 28)
  - 2-5-5, 73 Second St., Lot 35 (NYR 189), 1964-1966; 1970-1971 (Box 9, Folder 29)
  - 2-5-5, 75 Second St., Lot 36 (NYR 189), 1970-1973 (Box 9, Folder 30)
  - 2-5-5, 77 Second St., Lot 37 (NYR 189), 1957; 1966; 1970-1971 (Box 9, Folder 31)
  - 2-5-5, 79 Second St., Lot 38 (NYR 189), 1966; 1968-1970 (Box 9, Folder 32)
  - 2-5-5, 81 Second St., Lot 39 (NYR 189), 1966; 1970-1971 (Box 9, Folder 33)
  - 2-4-2, Lot 1-47 Second Street (NYR 189), 1966; 1971-1975 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - 2-4-2, 2-6 Smith St., Lot 16, 17, 18 (NYR 189), 1966; 1969-1970 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - 2-4-2, 8 Smith St., Lot 15, 21 (NYR 189), 1970-1971 (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - 2-4-2, 10 Smith St., Lot 14 (NYR 189), 1966; 1969-1970 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - 2-4-2, 12 Smith St., Lot 13 (NYR 189), 1966; 1969-1971 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - 2-4-2, 18-20 Smith St., Lot 9-11 (NYR 189), 1965; 1969-1971 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - 2-4-2, 22-24 Smith St., Lot 7-8 (NYR 189), 1939; 1969-1971 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - 2-4-2, 26-28 Smith St., Lot 5-6 (NYR 189), 1969-1971 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - 2-4-2, 30 Smith St., Lot 4 (NYR 189), 1961; 1969-1970 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - 2-4-2, 32-34 Smith St., Lot 2-3 (NYR 189), 1966; 1969-1971 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - 3-1-5, 40-42 Smith St., Lot 1 (NYR 189), 1969-1970; Undated (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - 3-1-5, 44-46 Smith St., Lot 2 (NYR 189), 1970 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - 3-1-5, 48-50 Smith St., Lot 3 (NYR 189), 1966; 1969-1971 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - 4-1-1, 62-64 South St., Lot 5 (NYR 189), 1970-1972 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - 4-1-1, 68 South St., Lot 4 (NYR 189), 1971-1972 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - 4-1-1, 70 South St., Lot 3 (NYR 189), 1966; 1968-1971 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - 4-1-1, 72 South St., Lot 2 (NYR 189), 1955; 1970-1971 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - 4-1-1, 74 South St., Lot 1 (NYR 189), 1970-1972 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - 77 South Street, Julian Russell, 1952 (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - 3-2-5, 81 South St., Lot 28 (NYR 189), 1966 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - 3-2-5, 83 South St., Lot 27 (NYR 189), 1957; 1966; 1970-1972 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - 3-2-5, 85 South Street, Lot 26 (NYR 189), 1956; 1966 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - 3-2-5, 87-93 South St., Lot 23-25 (NYR 189), 1960; 1970-1973 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - 4-5-2, 88 South St., Lot 54 (NYR 189), 1970-1971 (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - 4-5-2, 92 South St., Lot 55 (NYR 189), 1972; Undated (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - 1-1-4, 8 South Colden St., Lot 30 (NYR 189), 1966; 1972 (Box 15, Folder 37)
  - Block 1-1-2, Parcel 21, 9 South Colden St., Estate of Mary Lee McGill, 1973 (Box 8, Folder 34)
  - 1-1-4, 10 South Colden St., Lot 31 (NYR 189), 1968-1972 (Box 15, Folder 38)
  - 1-1-4, 12 South Colden St., Lot 32 (NYR 189), 1970-1971 (Box 15, Folder 39)
  - 1-1-4, 14 South Colden St., Lot 33 (NYR 189), 1954; 1970-1972 (Box 15, Folder 40)
  - 1-1-4, 16 South Colden Street (NYR 189), 1960; 1966; 1970 (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - 25 South Colden St., Lot 29 (NYR 189), 1965-1966; 1969-1970 (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - 1-1-2, 27 South Colden St., Lot 30 (NYR 189), 1962; 1969-1970 (Box 13, Folder 21)
  - 2-1-4, 1 South Water St., Lot 1 (NYR 189), 1955; 1966; 1970 (Box 6, Folder 29)
  - 2-1-3, 2 South Water St., Lot 60 (NYR 189), 1946; 1959; 1969-1970 (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - 2-1-4, 3-5 South Water St., Lot 2-3 (NYR 189), 1958; 1966; 1970-1971 (Box 6, Folder 30)
  - 2-1-3, 8 South Water St., Lot 58 (NYR 189), 1961; 1969-1970 (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - 2-1-3, 10 South Water St., Lot 57 (NYR 189), 1969-1974; 1976-1978 (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - 2-1-4, 7-13 South Water St., Lot 4-5 (NYR 189), 1966; 1970-1971 (Box 6, Folder 31)
  - 2-1-4, 15 South Water St., Lot 6 (NYR 189), 1966; 1970-1975 (Box 6, Folder 32)
  - 2-1-4, 17-19 South Water St., Lot 7 (NYR 189), 1959; 1966; 1969-1970 (Box 6, Folder 33)
  - 2-1-3, 20-22 South Water St., Lot 52-53 (NYR 189), 1954; 1967-1970 (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - 2-1-4, 21-25 South Water St., Lot 8-9 (NYR 189), 1966; 1970-1971 (Box 6, Folder 34)
  - 2-1-3, 26 South Water St., Lot 50 (NYR 189), 1970-1974; 1977 (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - Block 2-1-3, Parcel 50, 26 South Water, Paul M. Magliato, 1971 (Box 21, Folder 23)
  - 2-1-3, 28 South Water St., Lot 49 (NYR 189), 1966; 1969-1970 (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - 2-1-3, 30 South Water St., Lot 48 (NYR 189), 1970-1974 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - 2-1-3, 32-34 South Water St., Lot 47 (NYR 189), 1968-1970 (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - 2-1-3, 36 South Water St., Lot 46 (NYR 189), 1953; 1969-1970 (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - 2-1-3, 38 South Water St., Lot 45 (NYR 189), 1958; 1969 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - 2-1-3, 40-42 South Water St., Lot 43-44 (NYR 189), 1969; 1970-1974; 1978 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - 2-1-3, 44 South Water St., Lot 42 (NYR 189), 1957; 1969-1970 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - 2-1-3, 46 South Water St., Lot 41 (NYR 189), 1953; 1969-1973 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - 2-1-3, 48-52 South Water St., Lot 38-40 (NYR 189), 1948; 1964-1965; 1969-1970 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - 2-1-3, 58-62 South Water St., Lot 33-35 (NYR 189), 1949; 1969-1970; 1973-1974 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - 2-1-3, 64 South Water St., Lot 32 (NYR 189), 1949; 1969-1970 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - 2-1-3, 66 South Water St., Lot 31 (NYR 189), 1958; 1966; 1969-1970 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - 1-1-2, 68 South Water Street, Lot 17 (NYR 189), 1969-1970 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - 1-1-1, 70-72 South Water Street (NYR 189), 1964; 1969-1971 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - 1-1-2, 74 South Water Street (NYR 189), 1935; 1960; 1969-1970 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - 1-1-2, 76 South Water Street (NYR 189), 1962; 1966; 1969-1970 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - 1-1-2, 78 South Water Street Lot 12 (NYR 189), 1966-1970 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - 1-1-2, 80 South Water Street Lot 11 (NYR 189), 1946; 1968-1970 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - 1-1-2, Lots 7-10, 82-90 South Water Street (NYR 189), 1969; 1971-1975 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - 1-1-2, 92 South Water Street (NYR 189), 1969-1970 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - 1-1-2, 94 South Water Street (NYR 189), 1950; 1969-1970 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - 1-1-2, 96 South Water Street (NYR 189), 1948; 1953; 1966-1970 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - 1-1-2, 98 South Water St., Lot 2, 3, 32 (NYR 189), 1966; 1969-1970; 1986-1987 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - 1-1-2, 100-106 South Water Street (NYR 189), 1965-1969; 1970 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - 3-1-5, 43-45 Third St., Lot 4-5 (NYR 189), 1966; 1969-1970 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - 3-1-6, 44-46 Third Street Lot 3; 42-44 Third Street Lot 4; Rear Third Street Lot 5; 81 Water St. Lot 6; 91 Water St. Lot 10 (NYR 189), 1966; 1969-1970; Undated (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - 3-1-6, 48-54 Third Street Lot 1, 2 (NYR 189), 1954; 1969-1971 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - 3-2-4, 71 Third St., Lot 6 (NYR 189), 1965; 1966; 1970-1971 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - 3-2-4, 73 Third St., Lot 5A (NYR 189), 1953; 1957; 1970-1971 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - 3-2-4, 75 Third Street, Lot 5 (1 of 2) (NYR 189), 1972-1976 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - 3-2-4, 75 Third Street, Lot 5 (2 of 2) (NYR 189), 1972-1976 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - 3-2-4, 77 Third St., Lot 4 (NYR 189), 1950-1970; Undated (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - 3-2-4, 79 Third St., Lot 3 (NYR 189), 1970 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - 1-1-2, 1 Washington Pl. Lot 18 (NYR 189), 1954; 1966; 1970 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - 1-1-2, 3-5 Washington Pl. Lot 19 (NYR 189), 1970-1971 (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - 1-1-2, 7 Washington Pl. Lot 20 (NYR 189), 1970-1973 (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - 1-1-2, 11 Washington Place, Lot 22 (NYR 189), 1970-1972 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - 1-1-2, 13 Washington Place, South Colden, Lot 23 (NYR 189), 1966; 1969-1970 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - 15 Washington Place, Lot 24 (NYR 189), 1960; 1966-1970 (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - 1-1-2, 17 Washington Street, Lot 25 (NYR 189), 1954; 1966; 1970-1971 (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - 1-1-3, 18-20 Washington Place, Lot 28 (NYR 189), 1971-1972 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - 1-1-2, 19 Washington Place, Lot 26 (NYR 189), 1966; 1969-1970 (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - 1-102, 21 Washington Pl. Lot 27 (NYR 189), 1960; 1966-1970 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - 1-1-3, 22 Washington Place, Lot 29 (NYR 189), 1954; 1960; 1970-1971 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - 1-1-2, 23 Washington Pl. Lot 28 (NYR 189), 1951; 1969-1970 (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - 1-1-3, 24 Washington Place, Lot 30 (NYR 189), 1966; 1970-1972 (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - 1-1-3, 26-36 Washington Place, Lot 31-35 (NYR 189), 1951; 1966; 1970-1972 (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - 1-1-2, 29 Washington Place Lot 31 (NYR 189), 1954; 1968-1970 (Box 13, Folder 22)
  - 1-1-3, 48-50 Washington Street (NYR 189), 1957; 1961; 1970-1971 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - 1-1-3, 52 Washington Place, Lot 3 (NYR 189), 1957; 1966; 1970-1971 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - 1-1-3, 54-56 Washington Street, Lot 4-5 (NYR 189), 1957; 1959; 1970-1972 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - 1-1-3, 58-62 Washington Street 24-25 Lot 6-8 (NYR 189), 1959-1960; 1966; 1970-1971 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - 21 Washington Terrace, 1970 (Box 17, Folder 23)
  - Appraisal Parcel 25, 43-47 Washington Terrace, 1973 (Box 18, Folder 29)
  - Appraisal Parcel 26, 45-59 Washington Terrace, 1973 (Box 18, Folder 26)
  - Appraisal Parcel 28, 53-63 Washington Terrace, 1972 (Box 18, Folder 27)
  - 89-101 Washington Terrace, Appraisal Vermont Terminal Corporation, 1972 (Box 18, Folder 24)
  - Reuse Appraisal Parcel 16, 89-101 Washington Terrace, 1974 (Box 21, Folder 28)
  - 2-4-2, 1 Water St., Lot 19 (NYR 189), 1971-1975 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - 2-4-4, 2-4 Water St., Lot 13 (NYR 189), 1942; 1966; 1970 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - 2-4-2, 3-7 Water St., Lot 20 (NYR 189), 1969; 1970-1974 (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - 2-4-4, 6-10 Water St., Lots 10-12 (NYR 189), 1954; 1972-1976 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - 2-4-4, 6-10 Water St., Lot 10-12 (NYR 189), 1972; 1977 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - 2-4-2, 11-13 Water St., Lot 22 (NYR 189), 1964; 1969-1970 (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - 2-4-4, 12-14 Water St., Lot 8-9 (NYR 189), 1966; 1970 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - 2-4-2, 15-17 Water St., Lot 23 (NYR 189), 1969-1970 (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - 2-4-4, 16-18 Water St., Lot 7 (NYR 189), 1966; 1970-1971 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - 2-4-2, 19 Water St., Lot 12+24 (NYR 189), 1969-1971 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - 2-4-4, 20-24 Water St., Lot 5-6 (NYR 189), 1969-1972 (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - 2-4-2, 25-27 Water St., Lot 26 (NYR 189), 1966; 1969-1970 (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - 2-4-4, 26-28 Water St., Lot 3-4 (NYR 189), 1970-1971 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - 2-4-2, 29 Water St., Lot 27 (NYR 189), 1966; 1969-1970 (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - 2-4-4, 30 Water St., Lot 2 (NYR 189), 1969-1972 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - 2-4-2, 31 Water St., Lot 28 (NYR 189), 1966; 1969-1971 (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - 2-4-4, 32 Water St., Lot 1 (NYR 189), 1963; 1970-1973 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - 2-4-2, 33-35 Water St., Lot 29-30 (NYR 189), 1966; 1969-1971 (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - 2-4-2, 37-41 Water St., Lot 31 (NYR 189), 1947; 1968-1970 (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - 2-4-3, 38-40 Water St., Lot 9-10 (NYR 189), 1964; 1966; 1970-1973 (Box 5, Folder 39)
  - 2-4-3, 42-44 Water St., Lot 7 and 8 (NYR 189), 1966; 1972-1976 (Box 5, Folder 38)
  - 2-4-2, 43 Water St., Lot 32 (NYR 189), 1964; 1966; 1969-1970 (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - 2-4-2, 45-47 Water St., Lot 33 (NYR 189), 1966-1970 (Box 5, Folder 32)
  - 2-4-3, 46 Water St., Lot 6 (NYR 189), 1966; 1970 (Box 5, Folder 37)
  - 2-4-3, 48 Water St., Lot 5 (NYR 189), 1956; 1971-1975 (Box 5, Folder 36)
  - Block 2-4-3, Parcel 5, 48 Water Street (NYR 189), 1974 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - 2-4-2, 49-51 Water St., Lot 34 (NYR 189), 1966-1970 (Box 5, Folder 33)
  - 2-4-2, 53 Water St., Lot 35 (NYR 189), 1969-1974 (Box 5, Folder 34)
  - 2-4-2, 55-57 Water St., Lot 36 (NYR 189), 1963; 1966-1969 (Box 5, Folder 35)
  - 3-1-5, 59-63 Water St., Lot 12, 13 and 14 (NYR 189), 1966; 1969-1970; 1972-1973 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - 3-1-5, 65-67 Water St., Lot 11 (NYR 189), 1966; 1969-1971 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Block 3-1-9, Lot 1-5, 60-66 Water St. (NYR 189), 1963; 1967-1970 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Block 3-1-9, Lot 1-5, 60-66 Water Street (NYR 189), 1971 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - 3-1-9, 68 Water St., Lot 6 (NYR 189), 1966; 1970-1973 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - 3-1-5, 69 Water St., Lot 10 (NYR 189), 1966; 1969-1975 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - 3-1-9, 70 Water St., Lot 7 (NYR 189), 1966; 1970-1973 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - 3-1-5, 71 Water St., Lot 9 (NYR 189), 1965-1966; 1969-1970 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - 3-1-9, 72-78 Water St., Lot 8-9 (NYR 189), 1953-1987; Undated (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Block 3-1-9, Parcel 8-9, 72-78 Water St. (NYR 189), 1972 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - 3-1-5, 73 Water St., Lot 8 (NYR 189), 1962; 1966; 1969-1970 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - 3-1-5, 75 Water St., Lot 7 and rear of 6 (NYR 189), 1954; 1966; 1969-1970 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - 3-1-5, 77-79 Water St., Lot 6 (NYR 189), 1963-1964; 1966; 1969-1971; Undated (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - 3-1-10 80-84 Water St., Lot 1-3 (NYR 189), 1970-1971; 1973-1975 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - 3-1-6, 83-85 Water St., Lot 7 (NYR 189), 1966; 1970-1971; Undated (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - 3-1-10, Lot 4-6, 86-90 Water St. (NYR 189), 1971-1975; 1976-1977; Undated (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Block 3-1-10, Parcel 4-6, 86-90 Water St. (NYR 189) (1 of 2), 1972-1974 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Block 3-1-10, Parcel 4-6, 86-90 Water St. (NYR 189) (2 of 2), 1972-1974 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - 3-1-6, 87 Water St., Lot 8 (NYR 189), 1964; 1966; 1970-1971; Undated (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - 3-1-6, 89 Water St., Lot 9 (NYR 189), 1963; 1966; 1970 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - 3-1-10, 92 Water St., Lot 7 (NYR 189), 1953; 1970 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - 3-1-6, 93 Water St., Lot 11 (NYR 189), 1966; 1970-1971; Undated (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - 3-1-10, 94-106 Water St., Lot 8-11 (NYR 189), 1966; 1970-1971; 1976-1977 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - 3-1-6, 95 Water St., Lot 12 (NYR 189), 1966-1967; 1970-1971; 1973; Undated (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - 3-1-6, 97 Water St., Lot 13 (NYR 189), 1970-1974; Undated (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - 3-1-6, 99-101 Water St., Lot 14-15 (NYR 189), 1970-1975; Undated (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Block 3-1-6, 99-101 Water St., Parcels 14 and 15 (NYR 189), 1971 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - 3-1-6, 103-105 Water St., Lot 16 (NYR 189), 1966; 1970 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - 3-1-6, 107 Water St., Lot 17 (NYR 189), 1953; 1966; 1970 (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - 3-1-10, 108-112 Water St., Lot 12-13 (NYR 189), 1970-1971; 1973; 1975 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - 3-1-6, 109 Water St., Lot 18 (NYR 189), 1961; 1970-1971; 1973-1975; Undated (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Block 3-1-6, Parcel 18, 109 Water Street (NYR 189), 1971 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - 3-1-6, 111 Water St., Lot 19 (NYR 189), 1966; 1970-1971 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - 3-1-6, 113-115 Water St., Lot 20 (NYR 189), 1966; 1970 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - 3-1-10, 114-116 Water St., Lot 14-15 (NYR 189), 1966; 1973-1975 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - 4-3-2, 324-30 Water Street Lot 1-4 (NYR 189), 1970-1973; Undated (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - 4-3-1, 325 Water St., Lot 33 (NYR 189), 1972; 1976-1978 (Box 4, Folder 60)
  - Property Located on 325 Water Street City of Newburgh, 1975 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Appraisal of Property located at 327-329 Water Street (NYR 189), 1973 (Box 8, Folder 4)